sco.com 2004-10-09

# The SCO Group, Inc. | Company | SCO Privacy Policy

You can visit any part of [SCO's* Web site](http://www.sco.com/) without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, if you want to purchase a product from the SCO OpenStore, register a new product, sign up for a mailing list, enter a sweepstakes, or sign onto a page that requires authorization, you will be asked for your name, e-mail address, postal address, and other related information. 

This privacy notice contains the following statements:

  * Collecting and Using Information 
  * Purchasing Online Products 

**Collecting and Using Information**  
SCO may use "cookies" to learn about you and to remember you the next time you visit our Web site. That way, subsequent visits will be simpler and more seamless for you. If you want to manually control whether or not a cookie is used, you may be able to set your browser to do so. (For Web pages requiring authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will likely not be able to access those pages.)

SCO may track IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to keep track of a user's session, while the user's personal information remains totally anonymous. Tracking IP addresses can give us important information about our visitors. For example, we can learn which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they stay.

When SCO receives information about you or about your session, we may use it for research or to improve our site and the services we offer you. We may also ask if we may later contact you via e-mail or postal mail (for example, to send you information or special offers) or if we may share your personal information with other companies that offer related services.

**Purchasing Online Products**  
When you purchase products from our online store (OpenStore), we establish a "secure session" using the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. This protocol lets you securely pass information between systems by creating a private conversation that only your computer and SCO systems can understand (called "public key cryptography").

To benefit from the SSL technology, you will need an SSL-capable browser. Examples of browsers that support the SSL technology are Netscape® Navigator 2.0 and later, Microsoft® Internet Explorer 2.0 and later, and the 3.0 browser (and later) in America Online® for Windows. (For more details, see the documentation that came with your Web browser.)

* * *
